[music]
Hello flowers.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Welcome back to
another vlog. Vlogie vlog.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Yeah.
>> Um,
I'm shooting this intro after the fact.
So, I am going to go ahead and show you
what we did yesterday. Good morning,
friends.
Um, is it even morning? It's 1:00. Um, I
woke up,
watched a sermon, journaled, and now
it's 1:00. I have a spa treatment at
2:00. So, I just quickly want to take a
shower, get myself ready, and then go.
Um, I need to figure out this is not the
way that I want to start the vlog
because that's absolutely crazy. But, I
just want to quickly jump into the
shower and then we'll talk. And I also
want to charge my camera.
>> I'm in the car.
What's going on here? Um, my spa
treatment is at 2:00 and I still need to
find um I still need to find a
particular thing
parking. Everything seems full. It's a
public holiday today, so I'm sure
everyone is like this side. So,
um yeah,
just carry my camera properly.
I mean, my delusional self is telling me
that I can get there in like 5 minutes.
And I think I shouldn't overthink it a
lot. Like, I shouldn't try and get like
parking on the street. Like, I should
just find parking. Oopsie.
Go forward.
There we are, guys. the Balt um cars in
Cape Town,
the electric ones, they look like
Teslas.
Is that something that they have in
Jober as well or is it something that
they're just trying to roll out here in
Cape Town? Like what's the situation?
That's crazy. That's absolutely grizzly.
Okay. You could have driven though. Like
you literally could have driven. Okay, I
think that's the Why does my head look
so neat? That's so crazy.
Wow.
Okay. All the traffic lights are opening
for me. So, I guess that's
that's what I need right now.
Okay.
I wonder where I'm going to I'm going to
park. Oh, look at that traffic light
opening. You see what I mean?
Let me see if I can flip and show you
guys.
Can you guys see those cars? Probably
not.
Oh, THERE'S ANOTHER ONE. WHAT are these
cars? That's like four in the time space
of 2 minutes.
But that one wasn't even a bolt. That
was like a normal one, but I saw two
both like that and two normal ones. Is
that like the new car for Cape Town or
what? Like what is the car?
[screaming]
Okay.
Someone was over taking a taxi on my
lane. So, it's only right that I scream.
Guys,
I'm walking to the spa.
>> Is my shop open today? No, it's closed.
>> Really drive fast. I don't really drive.
>> Oh, there's another matcha place.
They're called Kova,
guys. There's a matcha play every corner
in Ka.
Okay, my parking is actually perfect
because
the hotel is right here.
To the hotel in 2 minutes.
It's right here by the corner.
Okay,
come back. The matcha place will still
be open.
When you're carrying a camera, it looks
like your son
of the week. So,
[music]
>> [music]
>> Yeah.
Ice
Yo [music]
on the beach. Shabbang. All of my ops
[music] they Why do they gas me up?
Where does it go? My head. How much I
got [music] a lot. Don't leave again. I
won't thinking and trying me do like
Bryson and [\h__\h] ass [\h__\h] don't [music]
can I forgive I can't what do I need I'm
here shorty keep asking the date she
trying to finesse [music] poly market
for bread where's the beef it's cooked
where's the boy he's [music] don't even
recognize none of these days at the top
of the charts I look am I upset [music]
a bit that's when you drop [\h__\h] I press
play on that ho [music] me skip skip
what should I Take a trip. Who should I
take this [\h__\h] Tennis lessons with a
Nike skirt on and a popping out your
head is [music] a goat. They need one.
The mirror's right here. I see one. My
[\h__\h] don't know how to pay me back. So
he saying that he catches a free one.
What kind of clip? Extendo. [music]
What kind of switch? Not Nintendo.
Hanging out with friends though. They
hanging out the [music] window. What's
up with gang? We back. What's in my
raps? It's facts. She said she miss me.
I caps it ain't better [music] than
that. Also in life is lit, but I know it
get better [singing] than that. I know
it get better than that. I know it get
better than that.
[music]
on the beach. All of my ops, [music]
they dead. Why do they gas me up?
>> We'll see you after my massage. Um,
[laughter]
>> let me enjoy y'all. Be safe. Bye-bye.
That was so good.
I'm so relaxed
and the pressure was perfect. Ask for
hard me. I want you.
>> That is probably the best massage. Like
that massage was so good. I had lunch
but videos were obviously not allowed
because again
[music]
>> um it was so good. I just want to get
home and sleep. Oh, that was so good.
Like guys, that was so good. I can't
express how good it was. Like, it was so
good. The pressure was hard. I love a
hard massage. And I don't know if you
guys remember
um one of my earlier vlogs, I expressed
how I struggle to relax in massages, but
I'm doing a better job at relaxing now.
So
that massage I always ask for hard um
thingy and it was so good like it was
hard and she kept on asking me are you
in pain and I'm like no no no it's not
pain but I obviously carry a lot of
tension on my shoulders and on my upper
back and I told her before we started I
said I probably have a million knots and
she said to me girl what are you doing
to your back like what is stressing you
so much. And to be fair, guys, this year
I haven't been stressed much. Like, I'm
just cruising. But one thing about me,
all the stress goes to my shoulders and
my back. It just affects my posture
down.
DJ Kelly [music]
DJ.
[music]
>> Another one.
>> We the best music.
>> I got home a while ago and I was just
chilling to be fair. Like my body I feel
like I'm going to I need like a good
8 hours sleep. But um I'm about to make
a quick pasta
and then I just got these two
and then muffins.
Um yeah,
so tomorrow I don't know what we're
going to do, but I feel like doing an
activity. I feel like I'm always within,
you know,
excuse I want to branch out.
excuse me, tomorrow.
Um, so I'm going to research a bit and
see. I just want to quickly [music] make
like a quick dinner
and then
Oh gosh.
Make a quick dinner and then
just sit on the couch. Maybe I'm going
to be bed by in bed by if I'm in bed by
11, then I can wake up at 8. If I'm in
bed by 9, then I can then if I'm in bed
by 12:00, then I can wake up at like
9:00.
But just 8 hours, then I'll be good.
The laziest meal I'm making, by the way.
I don't want to. Oh, I don't want to
even joke. This meal is going to be chop
chop chop. I don't even know if I'm
going to chop some onions.
But I don't think I do need to chop some
onions because I did Oh, there's no
onions in this.
Okay, let's see.
Hopefully,
I'm going to use drumsticks instead.
This is the laziest dinner, but I'm
hungry and I've told myself that I don't
want to eat takeaways.
Like, I'm so good. The last time I ate
out was on Saturday.
Yeah.
And I feel like
the food was really healthy. The
portions were small.
So
now just peeling an onion, guys.
Like you can't see what I'm doing, but
do I use the the choppy thing
[singing]
by
you?
My pasta,
my pasta is ready. I need to strain it
and keep just a bit of the pasta water.
Okay.
[music]
You have [music] to go slow,
but we go faster.
A little [music] better.
Slice it. Slice it. You know what that
means? I'm coming up on you quickly.
[music]
M I bring nice things.
Trying to get in bed. So [music]
stay
in [music] love, babe. What would I do?
If I didn't love you, babe, what would I
[singing and music] do?
I love you. [singing]
>> [music]
>> I want you to give you
[music]
your friends.
We need to go faster.
Tell me the best.
[music]
You know what that means? I'm coming up
on you quickly. M things
[music]
trying to
get something.
What would I do
about you?
What will I do?
I love you. [music] I do
love you.
[music]
Take off the basket. Okay.
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
>> I [music] want to be with you. I want to
be with you. I want to be with you. I
want to be with [music] you. I want to
be with you. Just
If I didn't where would you
if I been on my mind where [music] would
you still
keep it rather you trust me
[music] keep it don't got you got
nothing
I got something
[music]
we going to function
[music] like
side only
[music]
for life. Let's get it show to me.
[music] I know we're coming over.
I know what you need. [music] Already
on.
[music]
I'm going to enjoy my dinner. I will
speak to you guys later. Um, welcome
back to my channel. Welcome back to this
week's vlog. Thank you guys for watching
my vlogs. Thank you for interacting. And
thank you for being the best YouTube
community in the world. Let me just
boldly say, the flowers are the best.
Um, I'm still in Cape Town as I did say
that I'm going to be in Cape Town. Hey,
why are my legs dry here? What the hell?
When I have to put lotion. Still in Cape
Town. Um, still just chilling. Still
just living life. Um, I am going to
be here for another couple of days
before I have to head back to Joberg
because
um, this time because we have another
trip coming up and because I have to get
ready for that trip. So, I'm basically
going home, swapping out suitcases and
we go. Um,
right now we are about to start the day.
I'm heading to G Bay for the first time
and we're going on the train. How
exciting. Um, I told myself like this
time around I really want to explore. I
really want to just not be cooked up in
the house or not be within my vicinity,
but I just really want to branch out um
and just do things that I've never done
in Cape Town. Like I've never been to
Cal Bay, so that's very exciting. I've
been trying to shoot outfit videos. I'm
not too sure about the angle of today's
outfit video. I feel
my wig is starting to like get crusty.
It's oxidized. To be fair, I've had it
for
I haven't had it for that long. I'm
going to buy rubbing alcohol and some
wipes and just clean it up and then
restick it again. Camera is looking
there. Who doesn't know there Did I do
something? Why aren't you tracking my
face anymore? Okay, let me see. Auto
face auto detect
rotate view
that.
Okay.
[crying and screaming]
Okay, you guys, I fixed it. So, it's
fine. I need to get an Uber because I'm
going to take a train, guys. I'm so
like excited because obviously I've
never done that. But yeah,
[music]
there's another universe. Please make
[music] some noise.
Give me a sign.
This can't be life. [music]
If there's a point to losing love,
[singing] repeating pain, [music]
it's all the same.
I hate this place. Stuck in [singing]
this paradise. Don't believe [music] in
paradise.
Got to be more [music] sick of [singing]
>> almost passing with that trick.
[laughter]
for that guy.
>> That guy. Thank god he was ease
dropping.
>> Like next month come
here. [laughter]
>> We made it guys. Yo, we made it. But at
what cost? Hey.
>> The experience was nice though.
>> I guess we get up.
>> Yeah, I think so.
>> Do you think
>> I think it's there?
I think it's dreaming
[music and singing] of
real. [music] How am I still here? Just
seems so unfair. I could be wrong.
[music] If there's a point to be, but
[singing] there's where [music] we were
the good on the poor. I gave [singing]
it all I could. Stuck [music] in a
stone. All I see [singing] is everyone
baby. Is there
to be more to be more sick [music]
of his head in truth and thoughts the
paraly.
[music and singing]
[laughter]
I guess this is God rewarding us for
being obedient when he said don't get on
the train at so
[laughter]
you
>> this is so perfect like
>> I'm so sorry the penguin [laughter]
is 1864
>> how are you
>> thank you so much sir
>> good how are Are you?
>> I'm trying being you.
>> You've been trying since we got here. I
thought you were going to give me a
different answer this time.
>> Maybe say you are happier.
>> Yeah, [laughter]
>> you can't try always.
Sometimes you must just do sometimes you
just, you know, be out here. Spending
money isn't that.
>> No, spending money is not nice. Working
is good because you're making money.
>> Good.
>> Yes, working is good.
>> Wow. You're making money
cuz your time is money and [music] I
won't let them waste it.
Oh, no. No.
Baby,
just go with it. [music]
Cuz when you're with me, I can't explain
it. It's just different. We can take it
slow.
I can't help my [music]
basics.
[music]
He's [singing] a replace.
I'm not dangerous.
I'll be
Let's
But I'm not
worth
>> [music]
>> took me away. Your love ain't no amount
of time in this world. Me [music]
and just love me, baby. Feel it in your
[music] soul. Are you ready? I know your
heart been telling you you belong
[music] there.
Nanger.
>> Hi vlog. I just came from my run and I
met up with my girl.
>> Hey,
you probably already seen how hot they
look. I came from a run. So
um
Oh, this is so
Guys, even walking
[laughter]
because I'm never the friend
guys. Oh, don't [laughter]
if you have a good man in the comments.
>> Even a golden retriever is a doggy
[laughter]
at the end at the end of the day.
[laughter] Even a golden retriever is a
dog.
>> Oh my god. Like actually I think as
women let's all leave men and just live
on an island together
>> and leave men
what do you remember when we used to do
that on [laughter]
Tik Tok when people would like say bars
and then they be like what [laughter]
I'm I'm I'm like a JZ for real.
No, ask the people in your comics. They
know what
>> you what
>> I love Cape Town because it's seven and
we're just walking.
>> [laughter]
>> Why am I [laughter] honestly like
>> just take what you want, bro? Like, why
are you swearing at
>> like I'm inconveniencing you for my
stuff.
>> Why?
>> I don't get it. I know people who live
with bro said hi.
Oh my word. Anyway guys
>> and we can carry on walking. Yes.
>> Are you not tired?
>> I told you there's literally
you I was dying.
Not the small one, the big one.
>> Let me let me zoom. Let me
>> I become an elite athlete.
>> Yeah.
>> Mark my words.
>> I'm going to buy a mansion.
>> Yeah.
>> And it's just going to be me and B.
>> Yeah. So, please show them your thighs,
guys. This is what [laughter] they talk
about when they say thighs that save
lives.
>> I did it myself.
>> I did it.
>> [laughter]
>> I did it myself.
>> Yes.
I guys
it down.
[laughter]
>> What did they say? Throw something.
>> No. Um, I was in the branches.
>> Oh,
>> they thought you they thought you were
falling.
>> Sorry, love. They said yo. [laughter]
>> So charming.
>> Love women.
Even the way they said yo.
Even
walking away they say yo yo. [laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> There was this lady on my hike. She was
like her dog whenever she's walking with
a dog in SE.
>> There's so many rats here. It's crazy.
podcast,
>> guys. My sister,
my [laughter]
she said we're going on a hot girl walk.
Which we are, but please look at how
beautiful she looks.
[laughter]
You The more I look at you, the more
amazing you look. And then please look
at what I'm wearing. Show them [music]
>> it's cute.
>> I look like I'm going to the gym,
>> guys. I ended up changing [laughter]
>> and I look so cute. The other ones like
looked cute as well, but
yeah,
[laughter]
I wear your tracksuit now. I feel so
much better, guys.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
Oh,
>> extend. It has to be early morning or
>> like 6 almost.
>> Yeah, cuz it's okay.
Where's your future?
A hot girl walk, guys. Sorry. It started
off a bit chaotic, but me and my my
sister, we are just catching up.
guys. And it's not one of those like
where you say this is my family.
[laughter]
[music]
>> [music]
>> on your breath. Just [music] take it all
back. Take it all back, baby. Take it
back. Just take it all back. Take it
all. [music]
What you got to do? Give me all night.
[music]
Okay. Sorry.
>> Can we have tea?
>> Do you guys have like special teas?
>> Okay. So, like we have those are what
original
[music] white roses
and jelly different. [laughter]
You know what? I'm going to Oh, okay.
I'm going to have the imported jasmine.
>> Jasmine tea.
>> Yeah.
>> Hey,
do you guys have iced coffee?
>> Yes.
>> No, no, we don't have ice coffee.
>> We don't. Okay.
>> We used to, but we changed the menu.
>> Okay.
had a lot of stuff on this.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay.
>> Um, can I please have the J?
>> Does it come in a nice te?
>> Okay. All right. Thank you.
>> Thank you. [music]
I do me up all night. All night [music]
[music]
and we just don't get along.
You make me feel like I did you wrong.
Going places where you don't belong.
Ever since I left the city, you
you got exactly what you asked for.
[music]
Running out of places
you on my
[music]
used to me on my cell
night when you need [music] my love.
Call me on my cell phone.
Late night when [music] you need my love
and I know when that line [music]
can only mean one thing.
I know when that bl [music]
[singing]
>> What? How many KS are we on now? I
forgot to start it again. Ah, no. We
can't continue from where we were. Wait,
this cuz I ended it.
Okay. 7.5 7.5 km.
>> 10,000 steps.
>> We did it, Joe.
>> We did it. We're We did it, Joe.
>> That brings us to the end of our hot
girl walk family day.
Will I see you tomorrow? I don't know.
Oh, I think tomorrow I'm going to rest,
but I'm going to pick you up on Friday.
[laughter]
Goodbye, guys.
Good morning. Well, good afternoon,
guys. Good afternoon. I don't even want
to lie and say it's morning. I'm late as
not I won't say as always, but today I'm
late. Can you sit down, madame? Sit. Sit
down.
Um, this girl is going for a wash and
she's not sitting down. I'm not sure
where the style of not sitting down
she's taking from, but she knows that
when we're in the car, she has to sit
down. Can you sit down, girl? Can you
sit down? We have a minute to get to the
groomers. I'm probably going to have to
call them and tell them that we're
running late.
Guys, I'm going to talk to you when I
get there because I'm actually not sure
what is it that is dressing her. Was I
supposed to remove her leash? I'm just
not sure why she's so uncomfortable,
but again, all the traffic lights open
for me and we're going to get there in
the next 2 minutes. The only thing that
is going to be a problem for me is
parking.
Um, I've just dropped her off. She was a
bit agitated. I'm not sure why. Like,
she just wasn't sitting down. And she
usually gets into the car, sits down
like a sweet little girl. today. She was
[music] just going insane.
Um,
okay. But I think let's go to VNA.
I was thinking to be just local, but I'm
like, why not go to VNA? I haven't been
to VNA since I've got here. And
VNA actually fasting today. So before I
get out of the car, I just need to pray
and just, you know,
and just thank the Lord for sustaining
me because
um I didn't think I was going to make it
and it was heavy on my heart. I woke up
and went back to bed. Like I woke up to
pray to start the fast and then I went
back to bed and then I watched a sermon.
I journaled. I prayed and you know the
thing is it's like
one thing that I really enjoy about
fasting and I haven't been that great
with fasting this year which is [music]
not good. I haven't been fasting as much
as I should have is to just starve the
flesh. Starve the flesh so you can hear
God's voice clearly and to be filled
with peace. And you know one thing that
I learned about fasting that really set
me free is that you don't fast [music]
to change God's mind. you fast to hear
from him. So
yeah, so it it's just such [music] a
great thing to get used to. It's just
especially if you waiting for a word
from God, especially if you're waiting
to just hear a fresh word from God, like
it's good to fast. And if you just need
some wisdom,
it's such a good thing to do. So, and I
know we're not supposed to share when
we're fasting, which is fine because by
the time you guys see this, it will be
Sunday and I would have [music] been
done fasting. Today is Thursday. So,
yeah.
[music]
down
with my [\h__\h] Ruthless. We got
thutters in rounds, too. My [\h__\h] is mad
and bullshi.
My [\h__\h] are savage. Rofless. We got
rounds, too.
[music]
I swear to God, my clothes.
Switching my hoes like my flows.
Switching my flow like my clothes. She
won't shoot that gun over. [music]
Now she want my crew cuz the money come
all out the [music] roof. That [\h__\h] got
a ruar
58. [music] All of these [\h__\h] they
hate. Try to hide you through the gate.
No. Go to strip club, make it rain.
Yeah. So much money they use rates. They
[music] 100,000 in your face. Yeah. They
put 300 right in a safe. Met her today.
Yeah. She talked to me like she knew me.
Go to sleep in a jacuzzi. [music] Yeah.
Waking up right to a twopiece.
>> I close off the vlog. I'm at the airport
now. Um, thank you so much for reaching
this point. I had such a good time with
y'all and most importantly, this trip
was just so amazing. So healing in a way
and just like so special. I wouldn't say
healing per se, but I do think that it
felt like
I really found my spark in this trip.
Not to say that I felt like I'd lost my
spark, not at all. But I think coming
back to Cape Town when I'm when I'm in a
better headsp space mentally and just
career-wise, it felt really good because
I do feel as though like Cape Town was a
place of refuge to me when I was going
through everything that I was going
through. And I will say that the Cape
Town girdies and just all the people who
follow me, who are from here, whenever
they would bump into me last year, they
would encourage me and tell me to keep
going and they just showed me so much
kindness and I'll forever be grateful.
Just excited for what the rest of the
year has in store for us as a community.
Well, I love you guys and I will see you
on the next vlog. [music]